My advice to people around the world is that when a lady comes to you,
telling you that she has the spirit of this or that, please run away!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
My God.
Start again!
What I want to tell people around the whole world,
be careful of married women - some of them are married women;
they are looking for a place to pull you down.
They would be telling you, "Man of God, I am passing through this thing;
my belly is aching; I am having chest pain in the breast."
All this, all that - please run away!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Pastor, take your time and say it again.
You said that we should be careful...
Viewers all over the whole world, be careful
because this is how I just started following young ladies and married women.
They would come and say, "Man of God, I have pain in my waist; touch it!
Touch it and pray for me.
Man of God, I have pain in my chest; touch it and pray for me.
Man of God, my belly!" - before you know what is going on, you are on the other side.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
"Man of God, touch my chest; I have pain in my chest" - then I would lay my hands.
Then they would say, "Man of God, touch my waist; I have pain in the waist" - then I would lay my hands.
"Man of God, touch my tummy" - before you know it, from the tummy you have gone down.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The Synagogue Church Of All Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations, and Changing the world.
RV: Mel Flowers 30/03/2019